<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language version="1.0" htmlParse="true">
  <item id="btnContinue">Continue...</item>
  <item id="btnclose">Close</item>
  <item id="btnHelp">Help me!</item>
  <item id="btnAgreement">Most Like How I Think</item>
  <item id="btnNeutral">Neutral</item>
  <item id="btnDisagreement">Most Unlike How I Think</item>
  <item id="btnTransfer">Submit data</item>
  <item id="btnMail">Send via email</item>
  <item id="btnPrint">Print data</item>
  <item id="btnExit">Exit</item>
  <item id="selectItem">Please select...</item>
  <item id="errorHead">Error!</item>
  <item id="errorWindowTooSmall">Please maximise your browser for using this application.</item>
  <item id="welcomeHead">Welcome</item>
  <item id="welcomeText">This activity, that you will do now and then once more just before the Christmas break, will help you to write your reflective report. You are expected to write the report over the Christmas and exam period for submission at the start of semester 2. The report is worth 5% of the 20 credits for this module.{br}{br}Self reflection is not easy and this sorting activity will help you think about what is important to you.{br}{br}Please click on the continue-button.</item>
  <item id="loginHead">Student ID</item>
  <item id="loginText">Please enter your student ID.</item>
  <item id="loginFormHeader">Student ID</item>
  <item id="loginNoInput">Please insert your student ID.</item>
  <item id="loginInvalidInput">Student ID invalid</item>
  <item id="loginNoConnection">Connection to server failed. Please try again.</item>
  <item id="introHead">Introduction</item>
  <item id="introText">This exercise is to help you think about how you are developing as a computer scientist.{br}{br}Your tutor will be able to see what you have done, but this exercise is NOT assessed. It is only to help you with your assessed work. {br}{br}There are NO RIGHT OR WRONG ANSWERS!!! This is about YOUR views, YOUR learning, YOUR identity as a computer scientist.</item>
  <item id="step1Head">Step 1 of 5</item>
  <item id="step1Text">Read the following statements carefully and split them up into three piles: a pile for statements you feel are most LIKE how you think, a pile for cards you feel are most UNLIKE how you think, and a pile for the rest - statements that you feel less strongly about.{br}{br}You can either drag the cards into one of the three piles or press 1, 2, 3 on your keyboard. Changes can be made later.{br}{br}If you want to read this instruction a second time, press the help-button at the bottom right corner.</item>
  <item id="step2Head">Step 2 of 5</item>
  <item id="step2Text">Take the cards from the "MOST LIKE HOW I THINK"-pile and read them again. You can scroll through the statements by using the scroll bar. Next, select the two statements you feel are most like you and place them on right side of the grid.{br}{br}Now read the cards in the "MOST UNLIKE HOW I THINK"-pile again. Just like before, select the two statements that you feel are least like you and place them on the left side of the grid.{br}{br}Next, select the statements you think are second most like/most unlike how you think, and place them under "+3"/"-3". Follow this procedure for all cards in the "MOST LIKE HOW I THINK"- and "MOST UNLIKE HOW I THINK"-pile.{br}{br}Finally, read the "NEUTRAL"-cards again and arrange them in the remaining open boxes of the score sheet.</item>
  <item id="step3Head">Step 3 of 5</item>
  <item id="step3Text">Now you have placed all cards on the score sheet. Please go over your distribution once more and shift cards if you want to.</item>
  <item id="step4Head">Step 4 of 5</item>
  <item id="step4Text">Please explain why you feel the following statements you have placed below "+4" or "-4" are most or least like how you think.</item>
  <item id="step5Head">Step 5 of 5</item>
  <item id="step5Text">Finally, please answer the following questions.</item>
  <item id="transferHead">Submit Data</item>
  <item id="transferText">You've finished the survey. Please submit your data now.</item>
  <item id="transferFailed">Data submission failed. Please try again or mail your results via email/post.</item>
  <item id="transferOk">Your sort has been submitted successfully, and has been saved by the system.{br}{br}Please click "Exit" below to return to your sort history.</item>
  <item id="mailHead">Submit Data</item>
  <item id="mailText">You can either submit your data either via email or post. In the former case you'll need an email client like Outlook, in the latter a printer.</item>
  <item id="mailBody">Thank you for completing your sort.</item>
  <item id="printoutText">Please bring this printout to your tutor.</item>
</language>
